export default {
  title: "ㄷ ㄸ ㅌ",
  syllables: [
    {
      question: '도',
      options: "ㄷ ㄸ ㅌ",
      answer: 'ㄷ'
    },
    {
      question: '또',
options: "ㄷ ㄸ ㅌ",
      answer: 'ㄸ'
    },
    {
      question: '토',
options: "ㄷ ㄸ ㅌ",
      answer: 'ㅌ'
    },
    {
      question: '달',
options: "ㄷ ㄸ ㅌ",
      answer: 'ㄷ'
    },
    {
      question: '딸',
options: "ㄷ ㄸ ㅌ",
      answer: 'ㄸ'
    },
    {
      question: '탈',
options: "ㄷ ㄸ ㅌ",
      answer: 'ㅌ'
    },
    {
      question: '대',
options: "ㄷ ㄸ ㅌ",
      answer: 'ㄷ'
    },
    {
      question: '때',
options: "ㄷ ㄸ ㅌ",
      answer: 'ㄸ'
    },
    {
      question: '태',
options: "ㄷ ㄸ ㅌ",
      answer: 'ㅌ'
    },
    {
      question: '들',
options: "ㄷ ㄸ ㅌ",
      answer: 'ㄷ'
    },
    {
      question: '뜰',
options: "ㄷ ㄸ ㅌ",
      answer: 'ㄸ'
    },
    {
      question: '틀',
options: "ㄷ ㄸ ㅌ",
      answer: 'ㅌ'
    },
  ]
}
